Which one are you? Dabai, ready. Sixty-one, I will work for you until seventy-five. top secret aerospace,
He was beaten away by himself, and he was beaten away in a top-secret space flight. Let me see what equipment you have. Oh you,
Oh, come on, let's talk about those running games. Let's go.
I've been here before, brother, my golden egg, ah, the wind has changed to Tian Tiao, it's so smelly, two people,
One pair of twins and the other are sniping continuously. Where are your teammates? Brother, retreat. How can the other one move away?
Eat a bag? Ha, you will die if you eat it! The horse teeth from the labor area came over and the workers couldn't pull them out. There were a bunch of them in the blue.
Worker clothes and wheat should be eaten by those who run away from home. Eat them last because there are still people in the working areas.
Let's go to the garden and play slowly. I'm the host. Oops, add me again, don’t eat, don’t eat, don’t eat!
Brother, wait a minute. Look, brother, am I being persuaded to eat here a little longer?
Now one team is dead, two teams over there, one team here, three teams, four teams, plus the five teams running the knife,
The collection is live.
Let's go around in a circle to see if we can drive the centrifugal team over to fight them.
Then kill the rat head to remove the poison. Centrifuge and Ross Pier teammates have to walk down the slope.
Then add milk tonic, milk tonic, three, two, one, this part of the road, you detoxify. Go around now,
Kill those two teams, and then Wheat will take off his windbreaker and walk away to cleanse the poison.
Hey, hey, hey! Hey! Going around in a circle, Xida and Yiyuan are invincible when they open it. Brothers, they don’t even open it.
Uncomfortable. But neither of them are opened, and there is a way of playing without opening them, playing with high physical strength. Take a look, there is indeed someone there,
Did you see that? Don't hit him, just take your time. Zhong Wenqiao is at a bit of a disadvantage, but how can I help them? oh,
By the way, this is how you help your brothers. Come full circle and go to Blue Shoes.
Should I go see the seal rescue? If there is no way to save it, then it should be withdrawn. No? Saw it,
If you two get closer, you can see a white dragon. Oh, Pixel Yan Fu is useless, brother.
You are not Yan Fu of the Spirit Tree. You cannot die, you can only work as pixels. Pixel's Yan Fu doesn't work.
Wait for me, who has it? And, and people, and people. What about the radar team? Was blown away. Haha,
It’s so hard to give. Friend, if you keep pushing, we will retreat. That's right, let's evacuate together. I'll burn steel!
I don’t want it, I don’t want it, you take one, you take one, I know your insurance can’t fit, brother,
You take one, you choose one, you choose one, brother, I know your insurance can’t fit in it, OK, OK,
But he’s not stupid, he knows it’s expensive, hahahahaha, it’s okay, brother.
The first one is 7.8 million, brother, why are you throwing this away? Pick it up, pick it up! brother,
New heroes are coming, right? Brother, let me play. Come here, brother, don’t let me come inside.
Man, this.
No more tricks, brother! One shot sent me flying and I was killed by the explosion! I really can't stand you, to be honest,
Come on, bro, for a change.
What can be caught? What other cloth-enabled targets were obtained? Oh, how horrible! Get a beard, baby.
Ah! This one also has a low red card, otherwise I wouldn’t be able to lose so much money. Brother who shakes people, come here,
Later, brothers, start pretending. Do you really want to buy this? Uh, are you still doing the same old thing?
Come on brother, move in, brother move in.
Brother, hurry up! Did you still steal it? They were whipped, they were whipped. I'll fight you, go directly.
Hit one, one ed, one ed. o k o k o k,
Did we fall? No? Suddenly, a red wolf fell down and hit one on top.
Forget it, let’s not pursue it, right? You smoke it, this one is poured. Go up, go up, go up, go up.
Liu Tao, Liu Tao, I'm standing at our door and can't get out. Wow! Good brother, good brother, good brother,
Brother, brother, brother, brother, brother, brother, brother, brother, brother, brother, brother,
Brother, brother, brother, brother, brother, brother, brother, brother, brother, brother,
Let’s go, go travel, let’s go! Garden Garden, sure, sure, I had a bloody fight with him. Let's go, let's go, let's go,
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go,
This year, a man from Zhongqiao came. Zhongqiao called one and I gave him some food. Which one is it? What's good?
The main entrance is Zhongqiao. It should be added. Hey, it's beautiful. Yeah, which one? I'm awesome,
On the right is Wu Lulu, Wu Lulu, behind the box, run towards the stairs behind the box. Fallen, fallen,
It’s been a long time since it fell.
Hello, hello, hello! Hey, the one on the left, what a gun! Another one, run down the right, next track,
Next door, hey, six sets, six. I'm telling you, I'm telling you, they killed a team, they killed a team,
But, they are more than one team! I have to have a knife, then, that might clear it up, it's possible.